🛮 🕻 (+61) 466-624-891 | 🗖 siwoo.jg@gmail.com | 🎁 Gate 5 High St, UNSW Kensington, Australia, 2052 | 🗖 siwoojung

Summary_

A competitive individual in the hydrogen industry with various experiences from research and publication of a peer-reviewed journal article and employment at the industrial gas company as a process and project engineer. Currently commencing Master of Philosophy degree in the University of New South Wales, Australia, researching numerical designs of innovative and efficient metal hydride hydrogen storage tanks based on computational fluid dynamics.

Education

Master of Philosophy (M.Phil.) - Chemical Engineering

Sydney, Australia

University of New South Wales

Aug. 2022 - Current

Bachelor of Engineering (B.E.) - Honours, Chemical Engineering

Sydney, Australia

University of New South Wales

Feb. 2013 - Jan. 2019

Employment Experience

Project Engineer (Engineers Australia Accredited)

Yeosu, S.Korea

AIR LIQUIDE KOREA. CO., LTD.

Jul. 2020 - Apr. 2022

- Effectively managed the overall project activities during engineering, procurement, construction, commissioning and start-up phases.
- · Managed on-site construction activities as per the project contractual scope until handing-over to the operation team.
- · Participated in the project execution phase and created, modified and reviewed the technical documentation (P&ID, RFQ, PFD and others).
- Set up and supported cost estimation for new projects or modifications of existing plants.
- Responsible for technical decisions concerning construction, design, and selection of material, contractors and suppliers
- Coordinated legal permits related to KGS (Korea Gas Safety Corporation) and KOSHA (Korea Occupational Safety and Health Agency)
- Key project #1 Y4 CO2 Recycle Compressor Project CAPEX 6.1 mUSD from Dec. 2020 to Feb. 2022
- Key project #2 H2 Filling Compressor Project CAPEX 1.4 mUSD from Jul. 2020 to Dec. 2020

Process Engineer (Engineers Australia Accredited)

Yeosu, S.Korea

AIR LIQUIDE KOREA. CO., LTD.

Apr. 2019 - Jun. 2020

- Participated in the commissioning of a new plant project (Y4) pre-commissioning, commissioning, start-up and stabilizing.
- · Issued and updated technical documents, such as SOP and P&ID, of existing and the commissioning plant.
- Experienced field and board operations of new and existing plants in shifts for seven months.
- Modified and updated DCS (YOKOGAWA) and SCADA graphics.
- Managed safety and efficiency of plants.

Internship Seoul, S.Korea

BASF COMPANY LTD.

Oct. 2016 - Dec. 2016

• Worked as an intern in the finance & procurement team that mainly focuses on costs and expenses of BASF Korea for functional, sub-regional and business units.

Academic Experience _____

Research Assistant Sydney, Australia

FACULTY OF CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, UNIVERSITY OF NEW SOUTH WALES

Aug. 2022 - Current

- Project title: LAVO Hydrogen Storage Tank Modelling
- Industry-funded project RG222908 (\$111k) collaborated with the Australian start-up hydrogen company, LAVO
- Responsibility #1: Numerical simulation and validation and of LAVO's metal hydride hydrogen storage tanks, including modifications of operating parameters, boundary conditions, governing equations, etc.
- Responsibility #2: Numerical simulation and optimization of heat transfer management systems of LAVO's metal hydride hydrogen storage tanks, including geometry of tanks, internal coils & tubes, etc.

Poster Presentation Sydney, Australia

 $1ST\ University\ of\ Sydney\ Net\ Zero\ Initiative\ (NZI)\ Conference\ and\ 3rd\ Australian\ Circular\ Economy$

Nov. 2022

Conferences (ACEC)

• Numerical Modelling and Design of an Efficient Hydrogen Storage Tank Embedded with Copper Fins and Aluminium Foam

Poster Presentation

THE 2ND INTERNATIONAL SYMPOSIUM ON COMPUTATIONAL PARTICLE TECHNOLOGY

Melbourne, Australia
Dec. 2018

· Numerical Modelling and Design of an Efficient Hydrogen Storage Tank Embedded with Copper Fins and Aluminium Foam

1

Honours Thesis Sydney, Australia

FACULTY OF CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, UNIVERSITY OF NEW SOUTH WALES

• Numerical Modelling and Design of an Efficient Hydrogen Storage Tank Embedded with Copper Fins and Aluminium Foam

Dublications

Publications

Yuting, Z., **Siwoo, J.**, Yansong, S. (2021). Numerical Study of Hydrogen Desorption in an Innovative Metal Hydride Hydrogen Storage Tank. ACS Energy Fuels, 35 (13), 10908–10917. https://doi.org/10.1021/acs.energyfuels.1c00666

Honours & Awards

UNSW Tuition Fee Scholarship (TFS)

Sydney, Australia

FACULTY OF CHEMICAL ENGINEERING, UNIVERSITY OF NEW SOUTH WALES

2023

2018

• A Tuition Fee Scholarship (TFS) for study towards a Masters in the Faculty of Engineering in the University of New South Wales. TFS covers the entire tuition fee and the stipend valued at AUD 35,500 per annum for 2 years

Extracurricular Activity

Violinist

Various orchestra organizations 2001 - 2013

- Hwarang-elementary School Orchestra, South Korea (2001 2006)
- Nown-district Youth Sympony Orchestra, South Korea (2007 2009)
- Happy Jakarta Youth Orchestra, Indonesia (2010 2012)
- University of New South Wales Orchestra, Australia (2013)

Sergeant Soldier S.Korea

Full-time national military service Nov. 2014 - Aug. 2016

Dispatched interpreter Soldier

S.Korea

CONSEIL INTERNATIONAL DU SPORT MILITAIRE

Oct. 2015 Australia

Charity group member

Feb. 2017 - Nov. 2017

MISOJIDA, Korean Student Association, University of New South Wales

Technical Skills_

COMPUTER SOFTWARE

- · Ansys Fluent
- COMSOL Multiphysics
- AutoCAD
- High-Peformance-Computing (HPC): Gadi of NCI Australia and KATANA of UNSW

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE

- Python
- Java
- · C/C++

2